

CONTACT



045 356 1002



jessika.tyni02@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/jessika-tyni-806222220



jessika-tyni-portfolio.vercel.app



Finland, Tampere

SKILLS

- Team Work
- Adantahility
- Problem solving
- Verbal & Written

Communication

- Adobe creative cloud
- Project management

LANGUAGE

- English Fluent
- Finnish Native
- Swedish Basics
- Spanish Basics

JESSIKA TYNI

PASSIONED MARKETING STUDENT

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a second year Business Administration student from Häme University off Applied Sciences. I have 5 months of experience as a business administration intern at Häme University off Applied Sciences. Throughout my internship, I have gained hands-on experience in various aspects of marketing, including Adobe Creative Cloud software, team collaboration and planning and executing social media campaigns. Moreover, in my studies I have done multiple projects for companies, taken part in international projects and I am a member of my schools' Marketing team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Administration Intern, Häme University of Applied Sciences 14.11.2022 - 14.04.2023

Conference assistant, ITK- conference 5.10.2022 - 7.10.2022

As a conference assistant I learned problem solving, event

planning & people skills

Cleaner, Sol Oy, Mikkeli 17.5.2021-31.7.2021

As a cleaner I learned independence, problem solving & people skills

Mail distributor, Lahden Jakelut Oy, Lahti, 12.9.2018 - 24.10.2018

Achievements

I have taken part in multiple projects such as Novu collaboration and Erasmus+ projects during my high school years. During my bachelor studies I have been a conference assistant and currently I am a member of my schools' Marketing team and participating in an International product development project.

EDUCATION

Kannas Upper Secondary School 08/2018-06/2021

High School

Häme University of Applied Sciences 08/2021 -

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA